ZACK STOLZ

WORK HISTORY

IT Technician, 03/2019 to Current Resicap - Atlanta, Georgia

- · Corporate IT Operations, Support & Network Engineering
- · Troubleshoot and diagnosis hardware, software & network issues
- Patched software and installed new versions to eliminate security problems and protect data
- · Ticketing systems and hardware inventory
- Maintained (IDF/LAN) server rooms, wireless network and other server infrastructure, keeping systems running effectively and efficiently
- Vetting & Implementation of new procedures, network changes, and software/hardware standards
- · Developed and tested new product offerings prior to release.
- · Secure backups and data retention/migration
- · Re-imaging machines & Delegation procedures for damaged hardware
- Configured hardware, devices and software for new hire set up and terminated employee de-provisioning.
- Created support documentation that empowered and enabled user community to extend skills and leverage system features.
- System Administration via cloud based IT service providers

Tax & Compliance Analyst, 11/2016 to 03/2019 OnPay Inc - Atlanta, Ga

- · Account management
- · Successfully managed accounts of clientele in as many as 27 states
- · Completing ACH one off entries, penalty/interest liabilities & adjustments
- · Time management, file scheduling, and deadline drive projects
- Utilization of various software for long term retention of files, data archiving and file corrections

Onboarding & Implementation Specialist, 03/2016 to 12/2016 OnPay Inc - Atlanta, Ga

- Timely and accurately on-boarding clients with the software.
- Collecting all the appropriate data, documents and other information required for client integration.
- · Implementation of new Onboarding procedures and account set up.
- · Manual data entry/editing/manipulation within the software.
- · First response regarding risk assessments of fraudulent accounts.

Undergraduate Researcher, 01/2015 to 12/2015 University of Georgia - Athens, Ga

- Rotating studies (i.e. Cognitive, Existential, Comparative, Social, Observational, etc.)
- · Disclosure agreements, documentation and record upkeep
- · Data analysis and concluding research results.
- Managing research participants schedules, Accurate data management with research database.

CONTACT

Address: Atlanta, Georgia 30327

Phone: 706-273-9790 Email: zstolz26@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Skilled Technologist with experience configuring computers, servers and peripheral devices to work within established company and security parameters. Clear understanding of System Administration and IT Ops with online training in Web Development. Motivated to learn, grow and excel in a Development role.

SKILLS

- · Web Development
- · CSS, HTML, Bootstrap, WordPress
- · JavaScript & SQL
- · Technical support & analysis
- · Cloud based systems & System Administration
- · Ninja RMM & JumpCloud
- Ticketing systems
- · Quality, Compliance, & Organization
- · Troubleshooting and diagnostics
- · Analytical & creative problem solving
- · Scripting & Encryption
- · Microsoft & Adobe Suite

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science, Psychology, 2015 University of Georgia - Athens, Ga
GPA 3.65/4.0

Cum Laude Honors

Some College (No Degree), Web Development Treehouse & Udemy - Online

https://teamtreehouse.com/zacharystolz

Some College (No Degree)

Kennesaw State University - Kennesaw, Ga

Dean's List President's List ***Transfer to UGA